export const chapter = "Chapter - 9: fansen and His Teacher";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Who is the court-singer with the golden voice in the palace?",
          optionA: "Akbar",
          optionB: "Tansen",
          optionC: "The Empress",
          correctAnswer: "Tansen",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where did the Emperor Akbar sit when Tansen was singing in the palace?",
          optionA: "In the innermost heart of the Palace",
          optionB: "In the audience chamber",
          optionC: "In the corridors",
          correctAnswer: "In the audience chamber",
        },
        {
          question: "What effect did Tansen's singing have on the audience?",
          optionA: "It made them laugh",
          optionB: "It left them in enraptured silence",
          optionC: "It made them fall asleep",
          correctAnswer: "It left them in enraptured silence",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What was the Emperor Akbar's reaction to Tansen's singing?",
          optionA: "He scolded Tansen for disturbing the peace.",
          optionB: "He showered praises and gifts on Tansen.",
          optionC: "He left the chamber without a word.",
          correctAnswer: "He showered praises and gifts on Tansen.",
        },
        {
          question: "Who is the Guru of Tansen, the Saint-Singer?",
          optionA: "A famous musician from Akbar's court",
          optionB: "A hermit in the jungle of Brindaban",
          optionC: "Tansen's own father",
          correctAnswer: "A hermit in the jungle of Brindaban",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why did Tansen imitate the roar of a tiger when he was a child?",
          optionA: "To impress his father",
          optionB: "To keep people away from his fruit grove",
          optionC: "To entertain the villagers",
          correctAnswer: "To keep people away from his fruit grove",
        },
        {
          question: "What did the Saint-Singer promise Tansen's father?",
          optionA: "He promised to teach Tansen to become a great painter.",
          optionB:
            "He promised Tansen's father the reward of a world-famous singer.",
          optionC: "He promised to make Tansen a famous dancer.",
          correctAnswer:
            "He promised Tansen's father the reward of a world-famous singer.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where did the Emperor Akbar and Tansen go on a pilgrimage?",
          optionA: "To a distant kingdom",
          optionB: "To the palace of a neighboring king",
          optionC: "To Brindaban, the holiest ground in India",
          correctAnswer: "To Brindaban, the holiest ground in India",
        },
        {
          question: "What did the Saint-Singer Hari Das teach Tansen?",
          optionA: "How to become a great warrior",
          optionB: "How to become a world-famous chef",
          optionC: "How to sing and showered his affectionate love on him",
          correctAnswer:
            "How to sing and showered his affectionate love on him",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How long did Ah-ling stay with each of her sons as per her initial arrangement?",
          optionA: "Six months",
          optionB: "Three months",
          optionC: "One year",
          correctAnswer: "Three months",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "The palace was filled with the golden voice of the court-singer ____________. His limpid sweetness spread and echoed into the large chamber where the Emperor Akbar sat with his courtiers.",
          optionA: "Tansen",
          optionB: "Akbar",
          optionC: "Hari Das",
          correctAnswer: "Tansen",
        },
        {
          question:
            "After the singing ceased, many could be seen breathing hard, as if trying to come back to the real world from the dream world in which they had been venturing. Many eyes watered down as they recollected their past incidents, so impressive, heartwarming, and heart-touching the ____________ was.",
          optionA: "performance",
          optionB: "singing",
          optionC: "melody",
          correctAnswer: "singing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the audience chamber, Tansen, whose wonderful voice had roused memories - sad, sweet, and glad - in the hearts of the hearers, stood smiling before the Emperor who showered upon him praises and gifts because of the joy his ____________ had given him.",
          optionA: "performance",
          optionB: "voice",
          optionC: "presence",
          correctAnswer: "performance",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Of all his courtiers and subjects, Tansen was to him the dearest and best friend. It was his golden voice that filled the heavens with its ____________.",
          optionA: "beauty",
          optionB: "magic",
          optionC: "sound",
          correctAnswer: "beauty",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Emperor asked Tansen where the wonderful voice came from. Tansen replied, 'He is but a hermit, Sir, a saint who lives in the jungle of Brindaban. By all he is known as a holy man and his voice has the power of drawing all unto himself. Will not your majesty go with me on a ____________ to the holy forest where you may hear for yourself this voice of wonder?'",
          optionA: "journey",
          optionB: "pilgrimage",
          optionC: "vacation",
          correctAnswer: "pilgrimage",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The next day as the Emperor, seated on a huge elephant, started on a ____________ with Tansen to the latter's Guru, he said to the Singer, 'I wish to know one thing, 0 Tansen. How did you meet the Saint-Singer and how did you become his pupil?'",
          optionA: "visit",
          optionB: "journey",
          optionC: "quest",
          correctAnswer: "journey",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Guru lifted his voice and pealed forth the harmonies of Heavenly sounds. It told of the song of the stars, of the marriage of earth and seas, of the weavings of love, of the birth of Time and the crowning of Eternity, of the creation of gods and the dance of Love, each step of which is the making of a universe, each circle of which is the mutable law thereof. And, as he sang, Akbar fell on the ground drunk with the exquisite ____________.",
          optionA: "melody",
          optionB: "nectar",
          optionC: "music",
          correctAnswer: "nectar",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The pupil stood wrapped in devotion before that Saint-Singer, and when the singing ceased and its sweetness still throbbed through the silence of the evening, Tansen's hushed voice said to the holy man, 'The Emperor has come to pay you homage, 0 Guru.' And when Akbar had taken leave of the humble saint and had walked a little with his singer, he said, 'You are right, Tansen. He is all that you say. You are a shadow, he a sun. You are brass, he is gold. Why is this great difference and what is the cause behind it?'",
          optionA: "performance",
          optionB: "Guru",
          optionC: "saint",
          correctAnswer: "saint",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The difference, 0 Sir,' answered Tansen, 'is vast as you say, but the cause is simple. I sing to please an earthly King! He sings to please the King of Kings. You are a shadow, he a sun. You are brass, he is gold.",
          optionA: "melody",
          optionB: "performance",
          optionC: "purpose",
          correctAnswer: "purpose",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What did the casket actually contain when the sons opened it with the key? Ordinary ____________.",
          optionA: "gems",
          optionB: "pebbles",
          optionC: "money",
          correctAnswer: "pebbles",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Tansen was known for his melodious singing.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Emperor Akbar sat in the innermost heart of the palace during Tansen's performance.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen's singing left the audience feeling agitated and disturbed.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen's Guru, Hari Das, was a famous musician from Akbar's court.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen imitated the roar of a tiger to entertain the villagers in his childhood.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen's father was delighted when the Saint-Singer promised to make Tansen a famous singer.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Emperor Akbar and Tansen went on a pilgrimage to a distant kingdom.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen's Guru, Hari Das, opened the ornamental chest in the presence of Akbar.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen's Guru, Hari Das, had a voice that could draw people to him.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Tansen's singing was intended to please the earthly King, Akbar.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
